Are you all right?
I wonder what happened.
It seems as if the Alt-Noah Drive is offline.
But that's not possible.
The ships off Noah Drive was activated by her highness.
As long as she's still alive, it cannot be deactivated by anyone else.
As long as she's still alive?
Where is Salem?
Where is she?
Where's Salem?
Where is Salem?
How long will coffee be?
Water and water.
眩しい夜 who is singing then it will matter.
Where can I see the figure kommerssape?
I need ample patience
The light of blue sky
Somehow we are on the morning
For only one time
I will sing all our destruction
飛び立つよ
また空空へ
最大の思いがない
BMW車は
フルに立つ維づいた
タЬع độ
チェックス
合体効組
あたの
ピザ
水
どっか
アリエル
だった
中心
アレドブ Summen
ウェクト
アレドブ
イレビラス
イルミ忍
エケディー
yardım
ブック
エケディ
マーコ
ア Could
エirrel
Set countershock to two hundred joules.
Everyone clear.
Wait, maybe I should do it!
No, you're too light.
You think pretty fast.
We learned this in school.
Students never take it very seriously.
They laugh about doing the mouth-to-mouth.
It could save someone's life.
Want me to help out?
No, I can do it.
Your hands!
Oh, you made it.
Are you okay?
Inaho, is that you?
Where am I?
It looks like you passed out while taking a shower.
What happened?
I don't exactly...
I remember now.
I was attacked.
Don't move!
Wait, it was you?
Raiyei?
Why?
Where is the patient?
Get out of here now!
I said get out!
Everyone in the hallway!
Now!
We should probably do what she says.
Yeah, okay.
So who are you?
Tell us the truth.
Vercyan.
I was...
I come from Mars.
Why would you do this?
At the Shinawara parade,
the one who set up your assassination?
That man was my father.
He was a Martian spy living here on Earth.
He was promised the reward of a noble title if he killed you.
But after following his orders,
he was squashed like a bug,
just to silence him.
You can't ever trust any of the Martians!
Martians are all the enemy!
I can't ever go back to being a Martian.
I'm not a Terran either.
But you...
You revealed yourself as a Martian.
And in spite of that,
they accepted you.
You made a place for yourself among them.
Despite who and what you are!
He thought they were on the same side,
but they...
This is all your fault.
My father is dead because you came here.
This war started because you came here.
We were betrayed because you came here.
And now I'm alone because you came here.
Because you came here.
Because you came here!
How can these people not hate you for what you've done to us?
I'm so sorry.
You were right.
I've brought you all nothing but misery.
I was a fool.
Self-centered and vain.
M'lady, no!
I thought I was going to bring peace.
I thought that I could bring it about myself.
But really,
I was just acting like a spoiled child with a new toy.
The situation between our worlds is even worse than it was before.
Millions of people lost their lives.
No matter how much I tell myself that I did nothing wrong,
the reality is that all I did was bring misery to everyone.
But I am responsible for your family's tragedy.
I don't dare to ask for your forgiveness.
But I have to say,
I'm so sorry.
Why?
Why are you being so kind to me?
Don't you realize my father was trying to take your life,
and that I was just trying to kill you as well?
Why won't you hate me for that?
Why are you apologizing?
Why are you being so kind to me?
Why?
Tell me why.
How stupid are you?
Well, it's too late.
What am I even doing here?
Guess it's goodbye.
No, don't!
Why did you do that for?
The gun can't fire,
with the ejector slide open like that.
I knew if I had to take it away from you,
then that would stop it from firing.
No, I meant...
Honestly, I couldn't care less
whether you're a Terran or a Martian.
Our enemies are also enemies for you, too.
They want to kill you if they can.
But more importantly,
you fought with us on our side.
Are there any other reasons I need?
Do you really trust me?
I don't think that we're enemies at the present time.
But whether we're allies...
Well,
that's up to you.
You might come to regret this.
You're going into custody, of course.
Take her out of here.
Yes, ma'am.
Do whatever you want.
What do you have there?
Native Martian jewelry of some kind?
I was told it's a Terran good luck charm.
Dr. Yagarai,
how is our patient feeling now?
She seems to be fine.
But to stay on the safe side,
we ought to allow her to rest a little while longer.
I wish we could.
Unfortunately, I'm afraid she's needed.
I feel quite well.
Really, I do.
Oh, milady.
Captain, may I have a word with you?
Technically, that data is privileged information.
What is it?
It's a patient file for Lieutenant Marito.
Patient file?
It's also a prescription
that I think you need.
Prescription?
I wanted to thank you.
Huh?
This place here,
compared to where I've been sleeping,
is a paradise.
Hmm.
I'll know a drive.
Now online.
We're at full power, Captain.
We're good to go.
Then, Deucalion, raise ship.
That Raya girl's father
tries to assassinate the princess,
even though both of them are Martians.
Then other Martians kill her father.
So Raya grabs a gun and turns it on the princess,
even though she's a Martian, too.
And as for me,
well,
I shot the best friend I ever had.
So tell me, Humoray,
what was it like
to be killed by a friend?
Slaying.
I'd like you to look at these images
Of Tanegashima, where we found you
An enormous dock and shipbuilding facilities
You saw a ship there
Yes
And was that ship Alt-Noah powered?
Most likely
And was that Alt-Noah drive activated by Princess Asalem?
Hmm, you hold your tongue out of concern for her
Are you familiar with this?
What is it?
The Deucalion
A cataphract belonging to Viscountess Orlaine
That had gravitational control capabilities
Viscountess Orlaine?
The woman who was to have been my wife
We tried to create a better life
Using the power of Alt-Noah
Bestowed upon us by his majesty
We ruled well
We worked to cultivate the wastelands
To expand our domain
And to amass wealth
But no matter how we tried
We always ran into the same dead end
Obstacles
Obstacles?
The lack of water and air
At the time of the ancient civilization
That created Alt-Noah
Water and air were plentiful
But all that is left now
Is an atmosphere
Which is nearly vacuum
And what little water remains
Is underground
Because of that thin atmosphere
Verse is constantly swept by sandstorms
The harvest is meager
And only continues to diminish
As our population grows
We fall further behind
And become more impoverished
Trying to live on that world
Was always a short-sighted foolish plan
But our second emperor
His royal highness Gilzeria
Was a believer in the power of Alt-Noah
He focused his efforts
On growing our industrial capacity
The royal family
The keepers of Alt-Noah
Ruled with an iron fist
Turning a deaf ear
To the pleas of our suffering people
And then
The rising discontent of the populace
Was shifted to earth
The whole planet
Was then fed the belief
That it was the earth
That was at fault
With their claims of sovereignty
Political obstruction
Their denial of Vercyan independence
And attempts to rule us
From their distant world
That was the enemy to focus on
Everyone believed
And perpetuated the lies
Vercyans were the superior race
And the Terran subhumans
Who hoarded earth's bounty
Were evil
Plans were drawn up
To invade earth
We passed through the hypergate
And gathered our forces
Behind the moon
Foolishly believing
That our actions
Were just
Then as an advance party
We took my deoscuria
And Orlane's Deucalion
Down to Tanegashima
To gauge our enemy's strength
That was most unimpressive
Hardly worth expending the energy
To come down here to fight
They seem quite inferior
Don't you agree
My lord Sosbom?
Indeed
I'm quite disappointed
Orlane
It does mean
We shall be able
To take this planet
Far more easily
Than expected
Our people
Will be most pleased
And that will gratify
His majesty
What's happening?
Those are space-time
Distortion waves
They're growing stronger
The hypergate
The moon
Look
It's shattered
Orlane
We must withdraw
The surface is not safe
Withdraw
And it's Dorsus
They're affecting
My anti-gravity device
I can't fly
I'm on my way
You must not
It's too late my love
You must leave me
Hurry
I will have my revenge
For Orlane
Mark my words
But my lord
Count Sosbom
Calling UFE
This is the Deucalion
Headquarters
Request docking clearance
Welcome Deucalion
Clearance is granted
Burst your vessel
And dock 6
Deucalion
Acknowledged
I'm seeing this
With my own eyes
But I don't believe it
Battleship
Up in the sky
Looks like those
Japanese comic books
You read
I heard the project
Was abandoned
Because they couldn't
Activate its
Alnoa drive
Those reports
That they're harboring
Princesses Salem
Must be true
I was beginning to think
We'd never make it here
I know
United Forces of Earth HQ
Thank you
All stand by for touchdown
In 3
Ship landed
Engaging mooring
What a ride
I guess our voyage is over then
It is
For now anyway
For now ma'am
This ship
Now that we've got it
What is the enemy going to do
No telling
Everyone we've got it
Brought here is going to be safe
From now on right
This is a secret base
600 meters underground
Designed to handle
A nuclear strike
They say that a lot of refugees
Are being housed down
In these massive shelters here
They're supposed to have
Three years worth of supplies
Stockpiled
But apparently
The numbers don't add up
You mean to tell me
They're that much
Over their capacity
Just the opposite
It seems
Not enough in here
To use the supplies
It looks like the majority
Of refugees
Never made it here
If this got destroyed
It's possible that humans
On earth could go extinct
This is huge
Hey Inaho
I looked all around this place
And there's lots of
Arayons lined up over there
So why would you want to
Keep using that funky
Old slate mirror
Because I'm used to it
Just for that
Having heavier armor
Wouldn't have helped
Against anything
We've fought so far
Well suit yourself
If you're okay with it
So we still have to fight
We should sit back
And let the professionals
Do the job
Don't you think?
Doesn't hurt to be prepared
Look here
Oh it's got conformal
Power assist huh?
Old Noah
That is what started it all
I've come to say thank you
To you Inaho
I understand that once again
I owe you my life
No
This happens in war
And how many times
Does this make it now?
Should I start keeping track?
Don't know
And I wouldn't say
I've saved you yet
We are in a war
You're very kind aren't you?
Huh?
You really are
Tell me something
When this is over
We'll still be friends
Won't we?
We will
I'm very glad
Your highness
We have to go now
It is time
Very well
Let's go Adelritzo
We've much to do
Excuse us please
I am
A Salem verse
Lucia
I am the royal princess
Granddaughter of
Ray Regalia verse
Ravers
Emperor of verse
I address the people of verse
This war is meaningless
And I call for an immediate halt to it
I am safe
Alive and well
It was not the Terrans
Who made that attempt on my life
It was the orbital knights
Who want to invade Earth
The Terrans are blameless
Stop the fighting
Stop it now
Immediately
And make peace with Earth
I beg you
End this tragedy
Now
Wait is that
The Tharsis?
I liberated it
From Castle Cruteo
Because the Count
Was not worthy of it
It's all Noah drive
Is deactivated
Which means
Count Cruteo
Is truly dead
Princess Asalem's location
Has been pinpointed
Via laser transmission
To the moon base
And it is controlled
By those who share my vision
Her highness's heartfelt plea
Will not reach the ears of anyone
The final battle
Will be at the enemy's
Main stronghold
Even with the full might
Of a landing castle
It will not be easy
My debt to your father
Has been fully repaid
You may join my forces
If you wish
Or flee to the Earth
If that's your choice
Do as you will
My lord Saucebone
Launch preparations are complete
We await your command
Begin landing castle descent
The target
UFE headquarters
Navostadisk Russia
Hit the top—
It's here
We await
We amen
We at
Weitäten
We orbit
The word
watch
It's here
We oftentimes
We say
If there's any
We're let juegos
Tell us the devil at the moment,
Do not bite on your lap,
Run to them all alone.
Even though I call the
our
I say cry yeah, I say cry yeah, I say cry yeah, I say cry yeah, I say get the kind of sense so say
Woah, I say cry, I say cry, I say cry, hey say, you don't cry at my tears love
Let them back see that, see that it's beautiful, let them see you, my eyes and eyes and eyes.
Let them back see that, see that it's beautiful, let them see you, my eyes and eyes.